<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Extending the platform on</title><link>/extending/extending-platform/</link><description>Recent content in Extending the platform on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/extending/extending-platform/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create your own legacy services</title><link>/extending/extending-platform/create_your_own/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>/extending/extending-platform/create_your_own/</guid><description>You have the ability to create your own custom endpoints and seamlessly integrate them into your apps, enhancing the capabilities of Slingr according to your specific requirements. This is particularly useful for integrating with applications not covered by the official endpoints, utilizing existing libraries, and more.
The process of creating a new endpoint involves three fundamental steps:
Endpoint Creation: Design and set up your new endpoint. Testing via Proxy Endpoint: Thoroughly test your endpoint using the proxy endpoint.</description></item><item><title>Common features</title><link>/extending/extending-platform/common/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>/extending/extending-platform/common/</guid><description>👉 Endpoints, whether they are implemented in Java, Node.js, or another technology, share common elements such as:
- Descriptor File - Basic Settings - Deployment Settings - Stores - Functions - Events - Configuration - Scripts - Listeners - Flow Steps Descriptor file settings # The descriptor file, named endpoint.json, should be located at the root of your project. It contains the definition of your endpoint, including details like the name, type of endpoint, resources, functions, events, and configuration.</description></item><item><title>Java SDK</title><link>/extending/extending-platform/java-sdk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>/extending/extending-platform/java-sdk/</guid><description>This document will guide through the creation of an endpoint using the Java SDK and will provide details about the framework.
Crate your new endpoint project # To simplify the creation of a new endpoint, we provide a skeleton endpoint on GitHub. You can fork this repository, which contains the common features required for most endpoints. Visit the repository here.
You can also explore our sample endpoints to understand the features available in the Slingr integrations framework:</description></item><item><title>Node SDK</title><link>/extending/extending-platform/node-sdk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>/extending/extending-platform/node-sdk/</guid><description>Create your new endpoint project # To streamline the creation of a new endpoint, we offer a sample GitHub repository containing a skeleton endpoint. You can fork this repository to quickly access the common features most users require for their endpoints. Here&amp;rsquo;s the URL for the repository: Node.js Skeleton Endpoint
While you can certainly start building your endpoint from scratch, utilizing the skeleton endpoint can expedite your setup process.
Customize the skeleton template # If you&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to use the skeleton endpoint, there are a few adjustments you may want to make:</description></item><item><title>Proxy Endpoint</title><link>/extending/extending-platform/proxy-endpoint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>/extending/extending-platform/proxy-endpoint/</guid><description>Overview # This endpoint acts as a proxy for an endpoint running on your local server within the Slingr platform. It&amp;rsquo;s primarily designed for endpoint development. For more details, refer to the &amp;ldquo;Create Your Own Endpoint&amp;rdquo; section.
Configuration # Endpoint URI # The endpoint URI is the address at which both the external service and Slingr can locate your local endpoint. This should be a public URL (you might need to set up port forwarding on your router).</description></item></channel></rss>