<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Event Planner App on</title><link>/getting-started/getting/first-steps/event-planner/</link><description>Recent content in Event Planner App on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/getting-started/getting/first-steps/event-planner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About - Event Planner</title><link>/getting-started/getting/first-steps/event-planner/understanding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>/getting-started/getting/first-steps/event-planner/understanding/</guid><description>In this comprehensive tutorial, we will be working with the default app provided to all Slingr developers - the &amp;ldquo;Event Planner&amp;rdquo; app. Our goal is to empower you with the full potential of Slingr and guide you through your initial steps with the platform. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t created a Slingr account yet, you can easily create one here.
What is the &amp;ldquo;Event Planner&amp;rdquo; App? # The &amp;ldquo;Event Planner&amp;rdquo; app is a powerful application that comes pre-built with your new Slingr account.</description></item><item><title>First changes</title><link>/getting-started/getting/first-steps/event-planner/firstchanges/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>/getting-started/getting/first-steps/event-planner/firstchanges/</guid><description>In this section, we are going to take our first steps with the builder. If you are in the developer portal, you should see an app card similar to the one shown in the image:
Open the builder # 👉 Click on the button on the right (the one with the wrench icon 🔧 ) to open the builder in a new tab.
In this section, we are going to add a new field to the events.</description></item><item><title>First look at our new app</title><link>/getting-started/getting/first-steps/event-planner/firstlook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>/getting-started/getting/first-steps/event-planner/firstlook/</guid><description>In this section, we&amp;rsquo;ll review the changes made to our app in the previous section.
👉 First, open the developer portal and click on the runtime button (the square icon ) to open the runtime in a new tab.
👉 Navigate to the All Events section and select an event to open a read-only view.
👉 Click on the Edit button and change the status of the event to Cancel.</description></item><item><title>Creating actions</title><link>/getting-started/getting/first-steps/event-planner/creatingactions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>/getting-started/getting/first-steps/event-planner/creatingactions/</guid><description>In this section, we will learn how to add actions to our events. The purpose is to enable changing the event status without entering the edit view.
Create a &amp;lsquo;cancel event&amp;rsquo; action # Let&amp;rsquo;s get started by creating an action to cancel events using a feature called Flows. This action will only be visible when the current status of the event is set to Active. Follow these steps:
👉 Right-click on the node Model &amp;gt; Entities &amp;gt; Events &amp;gt; Actions and select New Action from the dropdown menu.</description></item><item><title>Actions in action</title><link>/getting-started/getting/first-steps/event-planner/actioninactions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>/getting-started/getting/first-steps/event-planner/actioninactions/</guid><description>In this section, we will explore how the actions implemented in the previous section work. To get started, follow these steps:
👉 Go to the &amp;quot;All Events&amp;quot; view.
👉 Click on a record to view its details. You should see the read-only view.
👉 In the header, you will notice a new button labeled &amp;ldquo;Actions.&amp;rdquo; Click on it to proceed.
👉 Both actions should now be visible, but please note that you will only see them if the status of the event is &amp;ldquo;Active.</description></item><item><title>Small change (optional)</title><link>/getting-started/getting/first-steps/event-planner/small/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>/getting-started/getting/first-steps/event-planner/small/</guid><description>One use that we could make with the field we have just created is to keep a correct track of all the events in the app. Currently, the Admin user of the app can delete events, which might be suitable in some cases, but let&amp;rsquo;s suppose that you want to manage it only with the &amp;ldquo;Cancel&amp;rdquo; status for better metrics in the future. We need to remove the permission for deleting an event from the Admin users.</description></item></channel></rss>