<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Task Manager App on </title>
    <link>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Task Manager App on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About - Task Manager</title>
      <link>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/creating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/creating/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Task Manager Tutorial!
What is a Task Manager App? # A task manager is an application designed to help individuals or teams organize, track, and manage tasks efficiently. It provides a centralized platform for creating, assigning, and monitoring tasks to streamline workflows and improve productivity. Users can set task deadlines, priorities, and statuses, enabling them to stay on top of their responsibilities and collaborate effectively with others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First steps - Builder</title>
      <link>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/firststeps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/firststeps/</guid>
      <description>Hi, welcome to the builder! Here, we are going to build the app. As you can see on the left, there is a tree with multiple items, we will call them: nodes. Let’s start building something great.
Creating the &amp;ldquo;Tasks&amp;rdquo; Entity # The tasks entity serves as the central component in the task manager application. It allows users to create, store, and manage task records efficiently. Through this entity, users can access various views of their tasks, granting them the flexibility to organize and handle records according to their preferences and needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First look at our App</title>
      <link>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/firstlook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/firstlook/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back! In this section, let&amp;rsquo;s take a first look at the app we&amp;rsquo;ve been working on. Although it&amp;rsquo;s currently a very basic setup, we&amp;rsquo;ll keep working on it to enhance its features.
Runtime Tasks grid view # 👉 If you followed the previous instructions correctly, your view should look similar to this:
Create a task # 👉 In the top-right corner of the view, you&amp;rsquo;ll find a Create button. Click on it, complete the form, and hit Create to see a read-only view of your new task:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding actions to an entity</title>
      <link>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/adding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/adding/</guid>
      <description>In this section, we will be working with the actions of an entity.
Let&#39;s go back to the builder and get to work. We already have the basic operations to create, edit, and delete tasks. However, it would be better to have a custom workflow that enforces some rules. For example, a task can only be moved to &amp;quot;In progress&amp;quot; if it is in the status &amp;quot;To do&amp;quot;. To create the workflow, we will:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing actions on runtime</title>
      <link>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/testing/</guid>
      <description>In this section, we will examine the functionality of the actions we implemented in the previous section.
Discover the actions # As you can observe in the grid view, a new column called &amp;ldquo;Actions&amp;rdquo; has been added. You can execute these actions from the &amp;ldquo;Actions&amp;rdquo; column or from the following locations:
From &amp;ldquo;All tasks&amp;rdquo; view actions column # From &amp;ldquo;All tasks&amp;rdquo; view main menu # From task record view main menu # Great!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a workflow view</title>
      <link>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/creatingworkflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/creatingworkflow/</guid>
      <description>At this point, we have an app with some fantastic features up and running. However, you might desire a different design for a specific use case. Let&amp;rsquo;s consider adding a workflow view to make our app look even more impressive. To provide you with a visual representation of what I mean, here&amp;rsquo;s an example of how it would look:
Create the workflow view # Isn&amp;rsquo;t it awesome? Let&amp;rsquo;s create the workflow view:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The workflow view</title>
      <link>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/workflowview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/workflowview/</guid>
      <description>Hi! In this section, we will take a look at the new Workflow View.
See the view # Make sure you are on the runtime of your app; if not, you can access it through the developer portal. Let&amp;rsquo;s see what we have accomplished. This is how the new Workflow View should look like after a few configurations.
We have built an awesome app. Let&amp;rsquo;s try it out and verify that the actions and transitions are working as expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Groups and permissions</title>
      <link>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/groups/</guid>
      <description>In this section, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover how to set up permissions in your Slingr app. We&amp;rsquo;ll create a new field for tasks to identify the user assigned to each task. Additionally, we&amp;rsquo;ll create two groups: Manager and Support. The users in the Manager group will have access to all tasks, while the users in the Support group will only be able to see tasks assigned to them and won&amp;rsquo;t be able to reassign tasks or change the task title.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing users and permissions</title>
      <link>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/testingusers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/testingusers/</guid>
      <description>In this section, we will test the different permissions and users that we created in the previous section.
Log in as a Developer # 👉 Log in to the runtime with your developer account (the same one we have been using). We don’t need to log in and out with the different users we created just for our app.
👉 Developers can switch users with a special feature that allows them to emulate other users, which is useful for testing different users and permissions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The app monitor</title>
      <link>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/monitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pmslingr.github.io/getting-started/getting/first-steps/task-mananger/monitor/</guid>
      <description>We have completed the development of our app, but it&amp;rsquo;s important to mention that you can monitor its activity using the app monitor.
Discover app monitor tool # To access the monitor, click on the Monitor button (the one with an eye) on the developer portal.
See the logs # On the app monitor, you can view information about your running apps. For example, you can see the logs of your app in the Logs section:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
